(Leonard:)You said candles were dangerous.
(Sheldon:)This is a Bunsen burner.
(Sheldon:)I'm a scientist. I know what I'm doing.
(Sheldon:)Oh, drat.
Oh. It took me a gallon of urine
to make that water.
(Leonard:)Listen, Sheldon, this is stupid.
I don't see why we can't be friends.
(Leonard:)I'm willing to drive you
and help you out with stuff...
(Leonard:)...I just don't want to
because of some agreement.
- What are you proposing?
- That we go back to the way things were.
(Leonard:)But when I do something for you,
you show a little appreciation.
(Sheldon:)How would I do that?
- You say "thank you."
- Every time?
(Leonard:)It's not crazy.
(Sheldon:)Counter-proposal.
(Sheldon:)We reinstate the full Roommate Agreement
with the following addendum:
(Sheldon:)In the spirit of Mother's Day
or Father's Day, once a year...